<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>driver-pilot.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <name>Driver Pilot</name>
  <summary>Smart GPU Driver Manager for Linux</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Driver Pilot is the ultimate tool for managing graphics drivers on Linux, specifically designed for NVIDIA and AMD users who want a hassle-free experience. 
      Whether you are a gamer, a developer, or just a daily user, Driver Pilot ensures your GPU runs at its best.
    </p>
    <p>
      <strong>Why use Driver Pilot?</strong>
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>
        <strong>Smart Express Install:</strong> Forget terminal commands. Our wizard analyzes your hardware and installs the perfect driver version automatically.
      </li>
      <li>
        <strong>Live Performance Hub:</strong> Monitor your GPU temperature, VRAM usage, CPU load, and RAM stats in real-time with a modern, beautiful dashboard.
      </li>
      <li>
        <strong>Laptop Mux Switch Control:</strong> Easily switch between Integrated (Intel) and Dedicated (NVIDIA) graphics to save battery or boost performance (Hybrid Graphics).
      </li>
      <li>
        <strong>Safety First:</strong> Built-in system diagnostics and Timeshift snapshot integration ensure you can always revert changes if something goes wrong.
      </li>
      <li>
        <strong>Gamer Friendly:</strong> One-click setup for Feral GameMode and Steam Flatpak fixes to optimize your gaming rig.
      </li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      Driver Pilot handles the complexity of repositories, kernel modules, and secure boot signing behind the scenes, leaving you with a clean and powerful interface.
    </p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">driver-pilot.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <!-- Screenshot placeholder or typically hosted URLs are used here -->
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/sopwith/driver-pilot</url>
  <developer_name>Sopwith OSDEV</developer_name>
  <update_contact>sopwith.osdev@gmail.com</update_contact>
</component>
